<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>net.pcsx2.PCSX2</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">net.pcsx2.PCSX2.desktop</launchable>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <translation type="gettext">pcsx2_Main</translation>
  <name>PCSX2</name>
  <developer_name>PCSX2</developer_name>
  <summary>A Playstation 2 emulator</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Emulador de Playstation 2</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Emulador de Playstation 2</summary>
    <screenshot>
      <image type="source">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/LeandroStanger/net.pcsx2.PCSX2/patch-1/PCSX2.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  <description>
    <p>PCSX2 is a Playstation 2 'emulator', a free program that tries to replicate the Playstation 2 console to enable you to play PS2 games on your PC.</p>
    <p>The advantages of using PCSX2:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Custom resolutions, up to 4096x4096, Anti Aliasing, and Texture filtering</li>
      <li>Unlimited memory cards</li>
      <li>Save states, enabling you to quick save and load practically anywhere in your game</li>
      <li>Easy cheating using our pnach patching system</li>
      <li>Use any controller or keyboards and mice</li>
      <li>Increase or decrease the game speed by using the built-in frame-limiter</li>
      <li>Ability to record in full HD with the built-in video recorder (F12 using the GSdx plugin)</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="pt_BR">
    <p>PCSX2 permite jogar jogos de PlayStation 2 no seu Computador.</p>
    <p>As vantagens de usar PCSX2:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Resoluções personalizadas, até 4096x4096, anti-aliasing e filtragem de texturas</li>
      <li>Cartões de memória ilimitados</li>
      <li>Salvar estados, permitindo que você salve e carregue rapidamente praticamente em qualquer lugar do seu jogo</li>
      <li>Fraude fácil usando nosso sistema de patch pnach</li>
      <li>Use qualquer controlador ou teclado e mouse</li>
      <li>Aumentar ou diminuir a velocidade do jogo usando o limitador de quadros incorporado</li>
      <li>Capacidade de gravar em full HD com o gravador de vídeo embutido (F12 usando o plugin GSdx)</li>
     </ul>
  </description>
  <description xml:lang="es">
    <p>PCSX2 le permite jugar juegos de PlayStation 2 en su ordenador.</p>
    <p>Las ventajas de utilizar PCSX2:</p>
    <Ul>
      <li>Resoluciones personalizadas, hasta 4096x4096, anti-aliasing y filtrado de texturas</li>
      <li>Tarjetas de memoria ilimitadas</li>
      <li>Guardar estados, permitiendo que usted salve y cargue rápidamente prácticamente en cualquier lugar de su juego</li>
      <li>Fraude fácil usando nuestro sistema de patch pnach</li>
      <li>Utilice cualquier controlador o teclado y ratón</li>
      <li>Aumentar o disminuir la velocidad del juego mediante el limitador de fotogramas incorporado</li>
      <li>Capacidad de grabar en full HD con el grabador de vídeo incorporado (F12 usando el plugin GSdx)</li>
     </Ul>
    </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://pcsx2.net</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/PCSX2/pcsx2/issues</url>
  <releases>
    <release date="2018-11-04" version="1.5.0-dev"/>
  </releases>
  <update_contact>tingping_at_tingping.se</update_contact>
</component>
